{"data":[{"question":"The founders of the American nature ________ the custom after the Revolution.","a":"reverse","b":"reversed","c":"has reversed","d":"had reversed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple Past: \n+ Express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (after the Revolution).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"When Bonaparte came along, he ________ it the law of the land.","a":"makes","b":"made","c":"has made","d":"had made","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Simple Past used with a duration which starts and stops in the past (When Bonaparte came along).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The king just ________ here yesterday.","a":"comes","b":"came","c":"has come","d":"had come","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (yesterday).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Many people ________ their jobs because of the firm's collapse.","a":"lose","b":"lost","c":"has lost","d":"had lost","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the past simple tense to express the idea that an action started and finished in the past","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ cleaning the floor, and now it's dirty again.","a":"just finish","b":"just finished","c":"have just finished","d":"had just finished","answer":"3","explain":"\n Present Perfect: \n+ Express action happened at an unspecified time before now. This tense emphasis the completion or result.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ a ghost in my life.","a":"never see","b":"never saw","c":"have never seen","d":"had never seen","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: used to describe your experience (the first\/the most...that; never, ever...).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"They ________ dinner before coming here.","a":"have","b":"had","c":"have had","d":"had had","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use past perfect to show that something happened before a specific time in the past.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"He waked up and down until he ________ by the returning warmth.","a":"is reassured","b":"was reassured","c":"has been reassured","d":"have been reassured","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Until + simple past, Past Perfect\/simple past tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I will wait until you ________ back.","a":"come","b":"came","c":"has came","d":"will come","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Future present tense until \/when\/as soon as\/ before + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"We always take out umbrellas with us when it ________.","a":"rains","b":"rained","c":"has rained","d":"had rained","answer":"1","explain":"- Two clauses are in present simple tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}